Finding Aid for Constance E. Cumbey papers, 1920-2004
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical Files
  - Group 2
    - Contemplative-type Religion (Box 29)
    - Controlled Disintegration (Box 29)
    - Co-operatives (Box 29)
    - Coors Family (Box 29)
    - Kenneth Copeland (Box 29)
    - Coptic Fellowship (Box 29)
    - Cornerstone Magazine (JPUSA, Jesus People USA) (Box 29)
    - Cornucopia Institute (Box 29)
    - Corporate Mind Control (Box 29)
    - Cosmic Awareness Communications, Inc., 2 folders (Box 29)
    - William Coulson, Council on Ethnopsychology (Box 29)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (C.F.R.) (Box 29)
    - Council for A Livable World (Box 29)
    - Council for National Policy (Box 29)
    - Course In Miracles (Box 29)
    - Phoebe Courtney (Box 29)
    - Norman Cousins, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Covenant House (Box 30)
    - Creation Social Science & Humanities Quarterly (Box 30)
    - Creationism (Box 30)
    - Creative Initiative (Box 30)
    - Credence Cassettes (Box 30)
    - Credit Card Developments (Box 30)
    - Cremation (Box 30)
    - Benjamin Creme (Tara Center), 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Benjamin Creme, Christian Responses, 4 folders (Box 30)
    - Crista Ministries (Box 30)
    - Critical Thinking (Box 30)
    - Critique Magazine (Box 30)
    - Royal Cronquist (Box 30)
    - CPOP (Church World Service / We Care, Inc.) (Box 30)
    - Philip Crosby Associates, Inc. (Box 30)
    - Aleister Crowley (Box 30)
    - Crystals (Box 30)
    - Cuba (Box 31)
    - Cult Analyses (Box 31)
    - Cult/New Age Brainwashing (Box 31)
    - Cult Fear Syndrome (Box 31)
    - Cult Murder Theories (Box 31)
    - Cultural Survival, Inc. (Box 31)
    - Cursillo Movement (Box 31)
    - Customs Procedures (Box 31)
    - Cybernetics (Box 31)
    - Czechoslovakia (Box 31)
    - Dalai Lama (Box 31)
    - Marci Dauer (Box 31)
    - Dead Sea Scrolls Project (Box 31)
    - Colin Deal (Box 31)
    - Death Education (Box 31)
    - Ed Decker (Box 31)
    - Declaration of Independence (Box 31)
    - Delaware (Box 31)
    - Deliverance Ministries (Box 31)
    - Delta Task Force (Box 31)
    - Gary DeMar (American Vision) (Box 31)
    - Democratic Party (Box 31)
    - Demons (Box 31)
    - John Denver (includes Audio Cassette) (Box 31)
    - Deprogramming (Box 31)
    - Desiderata (Box 31)
    - Destiny Image (Box 31)
    - DeVorss Publishing Company (Box 31)
    - Emily Dickinson (Box 31)
    - Disarmament Movement, 4 folders (Box 31)
    - Disciples of Christ (Box 32)
    - Distant Drums (Box 32)
    - Jeanne Dixon (Box 32)
    - Dr. James Dobson (Box 32)
    - Dominion Theology (Box 32)
    - Dominion Theology -- C.O.R.E. (Box 32)
    - Dr. Donaldson (Box 32)
    - Greg Donovan (Box 32)
    - Kevin Doran (Box 32)
    - Doubleday Religion Catalog (Box 32)
    - Dream Network Bulletin (Box 32)
    - Dream Themes (Box 32)
    - Drug Culture (Box 32)
    - Drug Treatment Programs (Box 32)
    - Druids (Box 32)
    - Druzes (Lebanon) (Box 32)
    - Duck Book (Box 32)
    - Dungeons and Dragons (Box 32)
    - Michael Dukakis (Box 32)
    - Eagle Forum (Box 32)
    - Eagle Forum (Schlafly) (Box 32)
    - Eagles' Reunion (Box 32)
    - Earthbank (Box 32)
    - Earth Community (Box 32)
    - Earth Day (Box 32)
    - Earth First (Box 32)
    - Earth Link (Box 32)
    - Earth Nation (Box 32)
    - Earthquakes (Box 32)
    - Earth Stewards Network (Box 32)
    - Earthwatch Institute (Box 32)
    - East/West Video Productions, Inc. (Box 32)
    - David Ebaugh Bible School, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - David Ebaugh, "Revelation Makes Sense," Registered Manuscript Copy 1968 (Box 32)
    - Eckankar (Box 33)
    - Economic Shock Testing (Box 33)
    - Economy (Box 33)
    - Ecumenical Movement (Box 33)
    - Education, 9 folders (Box 33)
    - Educators of Social Responsibility (Box 33)
    - Eficom (Box 33)
    - Egypt (Box 33)
    - Albert Einstein (Box 33)
    - Loren Eiseley (Box 33)
    - Elf Projects (Box 33)
    - Elfquest (Box 33)
    - T.S. Eliot (Box 33)
    - Emissaries of Divine Light, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Emissaries of Divine Light (cont.) (Box 34)
    - Emissary Publications (Box 34)
    - Encounter Groups (Box 34)
    - End-Time Handmaidens (Box 34)
    - Energies (Box 34)
    - England, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - Environmentalists (Box 34)
    - Epcot Center (Box 34)
    - Episcopal Church (Box 34)
    - Equal Relationships Institute (Box 34)
    - Werner Erhard Seminars Training (EST) (Box 34)
    - Esalen Institute (Box 34)
    - Esoteric Schools (Box 34)
    - ESP (Extra Sensory Perception) (Box 34)
    - Essene Bread (Box 34)
    - Eternity (Box 34)
    - Eternity Magazine (Box 34)
    - Eugenics (Box 34)
    - Euphorbics International (Box 34)
    - European Economic Community (EEC) (Box 34)
    - European New Age Activity (Box 34)
    - Euthanasia (Box 34)
    - Evangelical Apostasy (Box 34)
    - Evangelical New Age Conference (Box 34)
    - Evangelicals for Social Action (Box 34)
    - Evolution (Box 34)
    - Existential Psychotherapy (Box 34)
    - Exorcism (Box 34)
    - Mae Eye (Box 34)
    - Fabians (Box 34)
    - Facilitator (Box 34)
    - Facing Apocalypse Conference (Box 34)
    - Faith Healers (Box 34)
    - Rev. Jerry Falwell (Box 34)
    - Family Alternatives (Box 34)
    - Family Medication (Box 34)
    - Family Planning (Box 35)
    - The Farm (Box 35)
    - Farm Crisis (Box 35)
    - Father Seraphim Rose (Box 35)
    - Fatima (Box 35)
    - F.B.I. (Box 35)
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA) (Box 35)
    - Federal Reserve Board (Box 35)
    - Federated Organic Clubs of Michigan (Box 35)
    - Alan Shaw Feinstein (Box 35)
    - Feldenkrais Method (Box 35)
    - Fellowship In Prayer (Box 35)
    - Fellowship In Reconciliation (Box 35)
    - Feminist Movement (Box 35)
    - Debbie French (Box 35)
    - Catherine Fenner (Box 35)
    - Marilyn Ferguson (incl. correspondence re: lawsuit), 3 folders (Box 35)
    - Festivals (Box 35)
    - Fidelity Forum (Box 35)
    - Sam Fife The Move Examined, manuscript (Box 35)
    - Findhorn Foundation, 4 folders (Box 35)
    - Filioque Issue (Box 35)
    - Finger-painting Programs (Box 35)
    - Firewalking (Box 36)
    - First Amendment Organizations (Box 36)
    - The First Earth Battalion Foundation (Box 36)
    - The First Earth Battalion, Operations Manual (Box 36)
    - First Saturday Society (Box 36)
    - Florida, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - Food Control (Box 36)
    - The Force (Box 36)
    - Ford Motor Company (Box 36)
    - Fort Wayne, Indiana (Box 36)
    - Richard A. Foster (Box 36)
    - Foundation, "A Magazine For Biblical Fundamentalism" (Box 36)
    - Foundation For Human Understanding (Roy Masters) (Box 36)
    - Foundation For The Advancement of World Peace (Box 36)
    - Foundation For Inner Peace (Box 36)
    - Foundation of Universal Unity (Box 36)
    - 4-H Youth Programs (Box 36)
    - Matthew Fox, 6 folders (Box 36)
    - Peter Fraile (Box 36)
    - France (Box 36)
    - Franciscans (Box 36)
    - The Free Congress Research and Education Foundation (Box 36)
    - Freedom From Religion Foundation (Box 36)
    - Betty Freaue (Box 36)
    - Freemasonry, 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Freemasonry, Tracts and Pamphlets (Box 37)
    - Freeman Institute (Box 37)
    - Free Minds (Box 37)
    - Full Gospel Businessmen's Fellowship International (Box 37)
    - Fuller Seminary (Box 37)
    - Full Moon Group Meditation (Box 37)
    - R. Buckminster Fuller (Box 37)
    - Fund To Restore An Educated Electorate (F.R.E.E.) (Box 37)
    - Fundamentalism: Attacks On (Box 37)
    - Future In Our Hands (Box 37)
    - Futurists (Box 37)
    - Games (Box 37)
    - Garnett Foundation (Box 37)
    - Garabandal (Box 37)
    - Garvey Endeavors (Box 37)
    - Emil Gaverluk (Box 37)
    - Norman Geisler (Box 37)
    - Gematria (Box 37)
    - General Motors Corporation (Box 37)
    - Genetic Engineering (Box 37)
    - Georgia (Box 37)
    - Georgia, Atlanta (Box 37)
    - The Georgia Guidestones (Box 37)
    - Germany (Box 37)
    - German Marshall Fund Of The United States (Box 37)
    - Jack R. Gibb (Box 37)
    - Gifted Education Programs (Box 37)
    - Richard Gillman (Box 37)
    - Gimenez, Anne & John (Box 37)
    - Girl Scouts (Box 37)
    - Terri Griswold (Box 37)
    - Global Education (Box 37)
    - The Global Link Newsletter (Box 37)
    - Global Tomorrow Coalition (Box 37)
    - Global 2000 (Box 37)
    - Gnosticism (Box 37)
    - Goddess Worship (Box 38)
    - Frank Goines (Box 38)
    - God of Forces (The Force, Forces, Etc.) (Box 38)
    - Gold Lake Conference (Box 38)
    - Golden Lotus, Inc. (Box 38)
    - The Golden Thread (Box 38)
    - Stuart Goldman (Box 38)
    - Good News Network (Box 38)
    - Bill Gothard Seminars (Box 38)
    - "Bill Gothard's Sex Scandals -- Watergate? Or Waterloo?" by Rev. D.A. Waite (Box 38)
    - Government Funding and Establishment of New Age Religions (Box 38)
    - Kathleen Gow, Ph. D. (Box 38)
    - W.R. Grace & Company (Box 38)
    - Grace Newsletter, Tulsa, Oklahoma (Box 38)
    - Billy Graham (Box 38)
    - John Graham (Box 38)
    - Grail International, 2 folders (Box 38)
    - Greater Detroit Roundtable (Box 38)
    - Greater European Mission, Europe Report (Box 38)
    - The Great Invocation (Box 38)
    - Greek Mythology (Box 38)
    - Greening of Christianity (Box 38)
    - Greenpeace (Box 38)
    - Greens (Box 38)
    - Dick Gregory (Box 38)
    - Dale Griffiths, Ph. D. (Box 38)
    - Doug Groothuis (Box 38)
    - Ground Work (Box 38)
    - Group Consciousness (Box 38)
    - Growth Books (Box 38)
    - Norman Grubb (Box 38)
    - The Guardian Angels (Box 38)
    - Guidance Counseling (Box 38)
    - Guided Imagery (Box 38)
    - Bishop Thomas Gumbleton (Box 38)
    - Gurdjieff/Ouspensky Groups (Box 38)
    - Guru (Box 39)
    - Ben Haden (Box 39)
    - Kenneth Hagin Ministries (Box 39)
    - Manley Hall, Philosophical Research Society (Box 39)
    - Armand Hammer (Box 39)
    - Bill Hamon (Box 39)
    - Hands Across America (Box 39)
    - Hand Writing Analysis (Box 39)
    - Hare Krishna (Box 39)
    - Billy James Hargis (Box 39)
    - Billy James Hargis, Christian Estate Planning (Box 39)
    - William Harman, New Ager, on "Reconciliation of Science and Religion," February 1987 (Box 39)
    - Willis Harman (Box 39)
    - Harmonic Convergence, 4 folders (Box 39)
    - Harper & Row Publishers (Box 39)
    - Gary Hart (Box 39)
    - Hartley Films, "Films For The New Age" (Box 39)
    - Paul Harvey (Box 39)
    - Senator Mark Hatfield (Box 39)
    - Hawaii (Box 39)
    - Colleen Ballard Hayes (Box 39)
    - Kathleen Hayes (Box 39)
    - Father Edward Hays (Box 39)
    - Healing (Box 39)
    - Healing of the Memories (Box 39)
    - Health Foods (Box 39)
    - Mary Jo Heiland, Wichita, Kansas (Box 39)
    - Herbal Medicine (Box 39)
    - Heritage Foundation (Box 39)
    - Theodore Hesburg (Box 39)
    - Marilyn Hickey (Box 39)
    - High Frontier (Box 39)
    - High Wind Association (Box 40)
    - Highland Park Baptist Church (Box 40)
    - Hillsdale College, Imprimis Newsletter (Box 40)
    - Himalayan Institute (Box 40)
    - Hinduism (Box 40)
    - Hippocrates Health Institute (Box 40)
    - Holistic Counseling (Box 40)
    - Holistic Health, 8 folders (Box 40)
    - Holistic Living News (Box 40)
    - Holistic Nursing (Box 40)
    - Hollyhock Farms (Box 40)
    - Holography (Box 41)
    - Holy Blood, Holy Grail (Box 41)
    - Holy Order of Mans, 2 folders (Box 41)
    - The Homebringing Mission of Jesus Christ (Box 41)
    - Homeopathy (Box 41)
    - Home Education (Box 41)
    - Homosexuality [and AIDS], 3 folders (Box 41)
    - Hope of Israel (Box 41)
    - Hopi Indian Prophecies (Box 41)
    - Hospice (Box 41)
    - Hospitaller Cults (Box 41)
    - Hilton Hotema (Box 41)
    - House of Israel (Box 41)
    - House of Judah (Box 41)
    - Jean Houston (Box 41)
    - Wes Howard (Box 41)
    - Karen Hoyt (Box 41)
    - Barbara Marx Howard (incl. correspondence), 2 folders (Box 41)
    - L. Ron Hubbard, Dianetics (Box 41)
    - Dr. Hull (Box 42)
    - David Hulse (MSOG) (Box 42)
    - Human Events (Box 42)
    - Human Life International (Box 42)
    - Humanism (Box 42)
    - Humanistic Psychology (Box 42)
    - Human Potential Movement (Box 42)
    - Hunger Action Coalition (Box 42)
    - Hunger Ministries (Box 42)
    - The Hunger Project, 3 folders (Box 42)
    - David C. Hunt (incl. audio cassette and correspondence), 2 folders (Box 42)
    - David C. Hunt, "Deception" Screenplay by Tom McMahon and Charles Hadden (Box 42)
    - David C. Hunt Correspondence re: Inner Healing (Box 42)
    - Archbishop R. Hunthausen (Box 42)
    - Huntington House, Inc. (incl. correspondence re: Hidden Dangers Of The Rainbow) (Box 42)
    - Hypnosis (Box 42)
    - I Am Cult (Box 42)
    - I Ching (Box 42)
    - Idaho (Box 42)
    - Identity Movement, 4 folders (Box 43)
    - Identity Movement, Booklets, Pamphlets, and Tracts (Box 43)
    - Illinois (incl. photographic slides) (Box 43)
    - Illinois, Peoria (Box 43)
    - HIS Newsletter (Box 43)
    - The Illuminati (Box 43)
    - Imagery (Box 43)
    - In Context Magazine (Box 43)
    - Indexes (New Age Books) (Box 43)
    - India (Box 43)
    - Indiana (incl. postcards) (Box 43)
    - Industry (Box 43)
    - INFACT (Infant Formula Action Coalition) (Box 43)
    - Initiation (Box 43)
    - Inner Healing (Box 43)
    - Institute for Cultural Affairs, 6 folders (Box 44)
    - Institute of Noetic Sciences (Box 44)
    - Institute of Security and Cooperation in Outer Space (I.S.C.O.S.) (Box 44)
    - Institute Self Improvement (Box 44)
    - Institute for Spiritual Development (Box 44)
    - Institute for World Research (Box 44)
    - Institute for Divine Metaphysical Research, Inc. (Box 44)
    - Institute of Human Development (Box 44)
    - Institute of Judaic-Christian Research (Box 44)
    - Interlocking Directorates (Box 44)
    - Internal Revenue Service (Box 44)
    - International Center for Interactive Studies (Box 44)
    - International Cooperation Council (OCC), 3 folders (Box 44)
    - International Cops for Christ, Inc. (Box 44)
    - International Women in Leadership (Box 44)
    - Intervarsity Christian Fellowship (Box 44)
    - Iowa (Box 44)
    - Iran/Contra Hearings (Box 44)
    - Iridology (Box 44)
    - Israel (Box 44)
    - Illinois (Box 45)
    - Inner Peace Movement (Box 45)
    - Iowa (Box 45)
    - Insight Training Center (Box 45)
    - Institute of Advanced Thinking, Pasadena, California (Box 45)
    - Italy (Box 45)
    - Jesse Jackson (Box 45)
    - James C. Maloney, Retired Police Officer (Box 45)
    - Jamilian University (Box 45)
    - Japan, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Jehovah's Witnesses (Box 45)
    - Jeremiah Films (Box 45)
    - Jesuits (Box 45)
    - Jesus People USA (JPUSA) (Box 45)
    - Jews For Jesus (Box 45)
    - Jesus Only Movement (Box 45)
    - Jewish Messianic Expectations (Box 45)
    - Jewish New Age Materials (Box 45)
    - Joey R. Jochmans (Box 45)
    - John Birch Society, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - John David, Ph.D. (Box 45)
    - John F. Kennedy University (Box 45)
    - Jim Jones -- Jonestown (Box 45)
    - The Journal of Borderland Research (Box 45)
    - Jubilee Fellowship (Box 45)
    - C.J. Jung Institute (Box 45)
    - Jungian Groups (Box 45)
    - Kairos Foundation (Box 45)
    - Kansas (incl. photographs), 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Maureen Keaton (Box 46)
    - Jack Kemp (Box 46)
    - Kentucky (Box 46)
    - Ken Keyes Center, Coos Bay, Oregon (Box 46)
    - Khazar Jew Theories (Box 46)
    - Kinesiology (Box 46)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. (Box 46)
    - Kingdom Theology (Box 46)
    - Kingdom of Yahweh (Box 46)
    - Kinsey Report (Box 46)
    - Salem Kirban (Box 46)
    - Krikridge Foundation (Box 46)
    - Knights of Columbus (Box 46)
    - Knights of Malta, Order of St. John of Jerusalem (Box 46)
    - Charles Koch (Box 46)
    - Dr. Kurt Koch (Box 46)
    - Arthur Koestler (Box 46)
    - Milo Kovar, Astro-Pyschology Institute (Box 46)
    - Andre Kole (Box 46)
    - Delores Krieger (Box 46)
    - Kripalu Center (Box 46)
    - Krishnamurti (Box 46)
    - Elisabeth Kubler-Ross (Box 46)
    - Ku Klux Klan (Box 46)
    - Viktoras Kulvinskas (Box 46)
    - Kundulini Yoga (Box 46)
    - Kung Fu (Box 46)
    - Richard Kutsch (Box 46)
    - Jean LaBush and Brandy (Box 46)
    - Tim and Beverly LaHaye (Box 46)
    - Peter La Londe (Box 46)
    - Nora Lam (Box 46)
    - Lamsa Bible (Box 46)
    - Father Landinesser (Box 46)
    - Landkamer, Richard, "The Project" (incl. Corr. with Congressmen [copies] and FOIA Requests [copies]), 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Monica Lanza (Box 46)
    - Bob Larson Ministries (Box 46)
    - Bruce Larson (Box 46)
    - Last Trumpet Ministries, Beaver Dam, Wisconsin (Box 46)
    - Laser Technology (Box 46)
    - Lyndon LaRouche (Box 46)
    - Lyndon LaRouche (cont.), 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Lyndon LaRouche The Cult-Versus-Anticult Conspiracy to Bury Judeo-Christian Civilization (Box 47)
    - Lyndon LaRouche Secular Grass Roots -- Or New Age Front? (Box 47)
    - The Last Temptation of Christ (Box 47)
    - "Latter Rain" and "Restoration Movements," by Georgie Kinvon (Box 47)
    - Lusanne Committee for World Evangelization (Box 47)
    - William Law (Box 47)
    - Dr. Larry Lea (Box 47)
    - League for the Liberation
      - Assemblies 28-42, [under the auspices of The Foundation For Christian Economics] 1931-1932 (Box 47)
      - Assemblies 43-56 1932 (Box 47)
      - Liberation Magazine, 1932 (Box 47)
    - League of Nations (Box 47)
    - League of St. Paul the Apostle (Box 47)
    - The Learning Community (Box 47)
    - Dr. Timothy Leary (Box 47)
    - Lecture Outlines (Box 47)
    - Left/Right Brain Theories (Box 47)
    - Left Wing New Age Organizations (Box 47)
    - Legal Profession (Box 47)
    - Legislation (Box 47)
    - Peter Leithart (Box 47)
    - John Lennon (Box 47)
    - George Leonard (Box 47)
    - C.S. Lewis (Box 47)
    - David A. Lewis, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Flora Lewis (Box 47)
    - Liberation Theology (Box 47)
    - Liberty Lobby, 3 folders (Box 47)
    - Libya (Box 47)
    - Life Dynamics Fellowship (Box 47)
    - Life Discovery Principles (Box 47)
    - Life Extension Foundation (Box 47)
    - Lifespring (Box 47)
    - Light (Box 47)
    - Light Force Spirulina Company (Box 47)
    - Alfred M. Lilienthal (Box 47)
    - Lindisfarne Associates (William Irwin Thompson et. al.) (Box 48)
    - Hal Lindsey (Box 48)
    - Roy & Rae Livesey (Box 48)
    - The Living Word (Box 48)
    - Llewellyn Publications (Box 48)
    - The Lockman Foundation (Box 48)
    - Logos Bookstores (Box 48)
    - Lorian Association (Box 48)
      see also Spangler, David
    - Louisiana (Box 48)
    - Louisiana, Lafayette (Box 48)
    - Louisiana, New Orleans (Box 48)
    - Love Israel Foundation (Church of Armageddon) (Box 48)
    - The Love Project (Box 48)
    - Glen Lovelady (Box 48)
    - The Love Tapes (Box 48)
    - Lozamov Learning Method (Box 48)
    - George Lucas (Box 48)
    - Lucifer (Box 48)
    - Lucis Trust, 6 folders (Box 48)
    - Lowell Lundstrom (Box 48)
    - Lutheran (Box 48)
    - Lutherans Reformed for Truth (Box 48)
    - Lutheran East (Box 48)
    - Lutheran Apostasy (Box 49)
    - Lutherans, Missouri Synod (Box 49)
    - Barry MacIntosh (Box 49)
    - Shirley MacLaine, 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Pauline MacPhereson (Box 49)
    - Macrobiotics (Box 49)
    - Mafia (Box 49)
    - Mary Magdalene (Box 49)
    - Magicians (Box 49)
    - Maine (Box 49)
    - The Main Street Journal, 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Maitreya Buddha (Box 49)
    - Cindy Mallory, Revelation Theatre (Box 49)
    - Management Training (Box 49)
    - "Manifested Sons of God," by George Kinyon (Box 49)
    - Manna (Box 49)
    - "Manna," by Kim Vogler (Box 49)
    - Marantha Campus Ministries (Box 49)
    - Marantha, Exhibits 1 thru 18 (Box 49)
    - Marantha, Exhibits 19 thru 42 (Box 49)
    - Marantha, Exhibits 43 thru [blank] (Box 49)
    - Marantha, George Warnock (Box 49)
    - Mark-Age, I Am Nation (Box 49)
    - A. Jan Marcussen (Box 50)
    - Marian Movement of Priests, 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Daniel C. Markham (Box 50)
    - Tex Marrs (Box 50)
    - Catherine Marshall (Box 50)
    - George C. Marshall (Box 50)
    - Martial Arts (Box 50)
    - Dr. Jobe Martin (Box 50)
    - Malachi Martin (Box 50)
    - Ralph Martin Renewal Ministries, Ann Arbor, Mi. (incl. Corr.) (Box 50)
    - Marty Martin (Box 50)
    - Marxism (Box 50)
    - Mary (Box 50)
    - Maryknolls (Box 50)
    - Maryland, 3 folders (Box 50)
    - Masons (Box 50)
    - Massachusetts (Box 50)
    - The Master Game (Box 50)
    - The Master Key System (Box 50)
    - Roy Masters (Box 50)
    - Roy Masters Iconoclast Magazine (Box 50)
    - Jim Mathers, Mr. Steak (Box 50)
    - Mayans (Box 50)
    - Mayflower Bookstore (Box 51)
    - Dr. W.S. McBirnie (Box 51)
    - James McKeever End-Times News Digest, 2 folders (Box 51)
    - Elissa McLain (Box 51)
    - R.E. McMaster (Box 51)
    - Media (Box 51)
    - Media Spotlight, Al Dager (Box 51)
    - Medicine (Box 51)
    - Meditation (Box 51)
    - Meditation Magazine (Box 51)
    - Mediums (Box 51)
    - Edwin Meese (Box 51)
    - J. Gordon Melton (incl. Corr., Book Review of Hidden Dangers of the Rainbow) (Box 51)
    - Melanin (Box 51)
    - Menninger Foundation (Box 51)
    - Mennonites (Box 51)
    - Mensa International (Box 51)
    - Mercy College (Box 51)
    - Thomas Merton (Box 51)
    - Messiah Lutheran Church (Box 51)
    - Metaphysical (Box 51)
    - Metcalf (Box 52)
    - Mexico (Box 52)
    - Fr. Vincent Miceli (Box 52)
    - Johanna Michaelsen (Box 52)
    - Michelle Remembers Prophecies (Box 52)
    - Michigan, 4 folders (Box 52)
    - Michigan Coalition of Unregistered Churches (Box 52)
    - Michigan, Kalamazoo (Box 52)
    - Michigan, Lake Orion (Box 52)
    - Michigan Metaphysical Society (Box 52)
    - Michigan New Age Programs (Publicly Funded) (Box 52)
    - Middle Earth Books (Box 52)
    - The Midnight Call (Box 52)
    - Edward Miller, "I Looked And I Saw Visions of God" (Box 52)
    - Kim Miller (Box 52)
    - Betty Mills (Box 52)
    - Mind Control Systems (Box 52)
    - Minnesota (Box 52)
    - Miscellaneous Christian Pamphlets (Box 52)
    - Miscellaneous New Age Articles (Box 52)
    - Miscellaneous New Age Churches (Box 52)
    - Miscellaneous New Age Conferences (Box 52)
    - Miscellaneous New Age Directories / Calendars (Box 52)
    - Miscellaneous New Age Papers (Box 52)
    - Miscellaneous Protestant Ministries (Box 52)
    - The Mission (movie) (Box 53)
    - Missionary (Box 53)
    - Gerald & Patricia Mische (Box 53)
    - Mission of Maitreya (Box 53)
    - Mississippi (Box 53)
    - Missouri (Box 53)
    - Missouri, Kansas City (Box 53)
    - Missouri, St. Louis (Box 53)
    - Mockers & Scoffers (Box 53)
    - Modernism (Box 53)
    - Brig. Gen. Jack Mohr (Box 53)
    - Robert Monroe (Box 53)
    - Mondragon (Box 53)
    - Montana (Box 53)
    - Montessori Education (Box 53)
    - Ruth Montgomery (Box 53)
    - Mont Pelerin Society (Box 53)
    - Moody Monthly (Box 53)
    - Moon (Causa) (Box 53)
    - Moral Majority (Box 53)
    - Moral Rearmament (Box 53)
    - Dr. Morey (Box 53)
    - Mormonism, 2 folders (Box 53)
    - Mormons, "Ancient Texts and Mormonism," by Eugene Seaich (Box 53)
    - Barbara Morris (Box 53)
    - Barbara Morris Morris Report (Box 53)
    - Moslem (Box 53)
    - Mother Angelica (Box 53)
    - Mother Jones (Box 53)
    - Mother Teresa (Box 53)
    - Mt. Athos (Box 53)
    - Mt. Shasta (Box 53)
    - Movement for a New Society (MNS) (Box 53)
    - Movement of Spiritual Inner Awareness (MSIA) (Box 54)
    - Movies (New Age Influenced) (Box 54)
    - Eustace Mullins (Box 54)
    - Robert Muller, 2 folders (Box 54)
    - Multiple Level Marketing (Box 54)
    - Bob Mumford (Box 54)
    - Robert Murdoch (Box 54)